Finding Aid for American Society for Information Science and Technology Records, 1925-2001
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- ANNUAL MEETINGS
  - Individual Meetings
    - 1966 Santa Monica, CA
      - Exhibitors (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 150)
      - News Releases (Box 150)
      - Placement Service (Box 150)
      - Proceedings (Box 150)
      - Programs (Box 150)
      - Reports (Box 150)
      - Student Session (Box 150)
    - 1967 New York, NY
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 150)
      - Exhibitors (Box 150)
      - Final Reports (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 150)
      - Miscellanea (Box 150)
      - Office Meetings and Functions (Box 150)
      - Placement Service (Box 150)
      - Press Releases (Box 150)
      - Proceedings (Publication and Distribution) (Box 150)
      - Programs (Box 150)
      - Progress Reports (Meetings of Convention Committee) (Box 150)
    - 1968 Columbus, OH
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 150)
      - Evaluation (Box 150)
      - Exhibits (Box 150)
      - Final Reports (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 150)
      - Mailing List (Foreign) (Box 150)
      - Miscellanea (Box 150)
      - Placement Service (Box 150)
      - Program (Box 150)
      - Registration
        - Alphabetic Listing (Box 150)
        - Company (Box 150)
        - Zip Code (Box 150)
      - Schedule (Box 150)
      - Steering Committee includes Minutes (Box 150)
    - 1969 San Francisco, CA
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 150)
      - Awards (Box 150)
      - Chapter Assembly (Box 150)
      - Chapter Officers' Workshop (Box 150)
      - Evaluation by Donald W. King (Box 150)
      - Exhibitors (Box 150)
      - Final Program (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 150)
      - Hubert H. Humphrey (Box 150)
      - Mailing Lists (Box 150)
      - Miscellanea includes Forms and Procedures (Box 150)
      - NSF Grant Application: "Support for Innovative Presentations and Information Dissemination at a Technical Meeting" (Box 150)
      - News Releases (Box 150)
      - Placement Service (Box 150)
      - Proceedings, Modified Double KWIC Coordinate Index for (Box 150)
      - Proceedings, Publishers (Box 150)
      - Programs (Box 150)
      - Program Activity Notebook (Box 150)
      - Program, Technical (Box 150)
      - Publications Committee Minutes (Box 150)
      - Publicity (Box 150)
      - Registration Lists (Box 150)
      - Reports (Box 150)
      - Thesaurus Workshop (Box 150)
    - 1970 Philadelphia, PA
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 150)
      - Evaluation (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 150)
      - Miscellanea (Box 150)
      - News Releases (Box 150)
      - Placement Service (Box 150)
      - Proceedings (Box 150)
      - Program (Box 150)
      - Registration Lists (Box 150)
      - Report of the Public Relations Committee (Box 150)
      - Schedule of Council, Committee and SIG Meetings (Box 150)
      - Tutorial (Box 150)
      - Workshop: "Computer Photocomposition", 2 folders (Box 150)
    - 1971 Denver, CO
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 150)
      - Comments (Box 150)
      - Evaluation (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 150)
        (includes transactions for 1969-1970)
      - Miscellanea (Box 150)
      - News Releases (Box 150)
      - Placement Service (Box 150)
      - Proceedings (Box 150)
      - Proceedings Microfiche (Box 150)
      - Program: "Global and Long Distance Decision Making" (Box 150)
      - Programs (Box 150)
      - Registration (Box 150)
      - Reports (Box 150)
      - Speakers Handbook (Box 150)
      - Tutorials (Box 150)
    - 1972 Washington, D.C
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 150)
      - Conference Newsletter (Box 150)
      - Contributed Papers (Box 150)
      - Evaluation (Box 150)
      - Financial Information (Box 152)
      - International Information Retrieval Network (Box 152)
      - Miscellanea (Box 152)
      - News Releases (Box 152)
      - Open Forum (Box 152)
      - Program (Box 152)
    - 1972 Mid-Year Meeting: Dayton, OH (Box 152)
    - 1973 Los Angeles, CA
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 152)
      - Miscellanea (Box 152)
      - Open Forum (Box 152)
      - Program (Box 152)
    - 1973 Mid-Year Meeting: Bloomington, MN (Box 152)
    - 1974 Atlanta, GA, 1974
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 152)
      - Evaluation (Box 152)
      - Exhibitors (Box 152)
      - Financial Information (Box 152)
      - Miscellanea (Box 152)
      - Open Forum (Box 152)
      - Participants (Box 152)
      - Placement Service (Box 152)
      - Program (Box 152)
    - 1974 Mid-Year Meeting: Johnston, PA (Box 152)
    - 1975 Boston, MA
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 152)
      - Evaluation (Box 152)
      - Exhibitors (Box 152)
      - Financial Information (Box 152)
      - Keynote Address (Box 152)
      - Miscellanea (Box 152)
      - Open Forum (Box 152)
      - Photographs (Box 152)
      - Placement Service
        - Employee Resumes (Box 152)
        - Employer Listings (Box 152)
      - Program (Box 152)
      - Registration (Box 152)
      - Workshop: "Project to Investigate the Planning Requirements of the STI Community" (Box 152)
    - 1975 Mid-Year Meeting: Portland, OR (Box 152)
    - 1976 Bicentennial Meeting, Washington, DC
      - Addresses (Box 152)
      - Application for Recognition from the American Revolution Bicentennial Administration (Box 152)
      - American Revolution Bicentennial Committee
        - Relations with ASIS (Box 152)
        - Ruth Tighe's Files (Box 152)
      - Artifacts includes Correspondence and Photographs for Display (Box 152)
      - Articles about Meeting for BASIS, 3 folders (Box 152)
      - Career Counseling (Box 153)
      - Career Profile Contest (Box 153)
      - Committee Minutes (Box 153)
      - Correspondence (Box 153)
      - Exhibits (Box 153)
      - FOIA (Freedom of Information Act) (Box 153)
      - Financial Information (Box 153)
      - Funding (Box 153)
      - Mailing Lists (Box 153)
      - Miscellanea, 3 folders (Box 153)
      - Morentz Copies (Box 153)
      - News Releases (Box 153)
      - Participants/Speakers (Box 153)
        (includes letter from Hubert H. Humphrey)
      - Photographs (Box 153)
      - Post Conference Reports (Box 153)
      - Program (Box 153)
      - SYNCON (Synergistic Convergence)
        - Discussion Guides (Box 153)
        - Miscellanea (Box 153)
        - Participants (Box 153)
        - Reports (Box 153)
    - 1976 San Francisco, CA
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 153)
      - Committee Minutes (Box 153)
      - FID-ASIS Cooperative Arrangements (Box 153)
      - Financial Information (Box 153)
      - Miscellanea (Box 153)
      - Open Forum (Box 153)
      - Paper Presenters (Box 153)
      - Placement Service (Box 153)
      - Program (Box 153)
      - Registration (Box 153)
    - 1977 Chicago, IL
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 153)
      - Correspondence (Box 153)
      - Exhibits (Box 153)
      - Financial Information (Box 153)
      - Open Forum (Box 153)
    - 1977 Mid-Year Meeting: Syracuse University, Syracuse, NY (Box 153)
    - 1978 New York, NY
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 153)
      - Conference Management Manual (Box 153)
      - Correspondence (Box 153)
      - Doctoral Forum (Box 153)
      - Exhibits (Box 153)
      - Financial Information (Box 153)
      - Information Science Theater (Box 153)
      - Minutes (Box 153)
      - Miscellanea includes Photographs (Box 153)
      - News Releases (Box 153)
      - Newsletters (Box 153)
      - Open Forum (Box 153)
      - Placement Service (Box 153)
      - Programs (Box 153)
      - Registration Lists
        - Chapters (Box 153)
        - Company/Organization Affiliation (Box 153)
        - General (Box 153)
        - Non-U.S. Attendees (Box 153)
        - SIG (Box 153)
      - SIG Rush (Box 153)
      - Telecommunications (Box 153)
      - Workshops (Box 153)
    - 1978 Mid-Year Meeting: Houston, TX, 1978 (Box 153)
    - 1979 Minneapolis, MN
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 153)
      - Attendees (Box 153)
      - Correspondence (Box 153)
      - Doctoral Forum (Box 153)
      - Evaluation (Box 153)
      - Exhibits (Box 153)
      - FID (Box 153)
      - Financial Information (Box 154)
      - Information Science Theater (Box 154)
      - Minutes (Box 154)
      - Miscellanea, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Newsletters (Box 154)
      - Placement Service (Box 154)
      - News Releases (Box 154)
      - Proceedings: table of contents, index (Box 154)
      - Program (Box 154)
      - Registration List (Box 154)
      - Sessions (Box 154)
      - Workshops (Box 154)
    - 1979 Mid-Year Meeting: Banff, Alberta, Canada
      - Financial Information (Box 154)
      - Registration (Box 154)
    - 1980 Anaheim, CA
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 154)
      - Career Advisory Service (Box 154)
      - Career Development Forum (Box 154)
      - Doctoral Forum (Box 154)
      - Evaluation (Box 154)
      - Exhibitors Reservations (Box 154)
      - Exhibits (Box 154)
      - Financial Information (Box 154)
      - Information Science Theater (Box 154)
      - Miscellanea (Box 154)
      - News Releases (Box 154)
      - Newsletters (Box 154)
      - Photographs (Box 154)
      - Programs (Box 154)
      - Registration (Box 154)
      - Steering Committee Minutes (Box 154)
      - Survey (Box 154)
      - Workshop (Box 154)
    - 1980 Mid-Year Meeting: Pittsburgh, PA
      - Financial Information (Box 154)
      - Miscellanea (Box 154)
      - Papers (Box 154)
      - Presidents' Forum (Box 154)
      - Program (Box 154)
      - Report (Box 154)
      - Speakers (Box 154)
    - 1981 Washington, DC
      - Annual Business Meeting (Box 154)
      - Career Advisory Service (Box 154)
      - Committee (Box 154)
      - Doctoral Forum (Box 154)
      - Evaluation (Box 154)
      - Exhibitors Lists (Box 154)
      - Exhibits (Box 154)
      - Financial Information (Box 154)
      - Information Science Theater (Box 154)
      - Minutes (Box 154)
      - Miscellanea (Box 154)
      - News Releases (Box 154)
      - Program (Box 154)
    - 1981 Mid-Year Meeting: Durango, CO (Box 154)
    - 1982 Columbus, OH
      - Annual Meeting Committee Minutes, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Committee Reports, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Conference and Meetings Report (Final draft) (Box 154)
      - Financial Information (Box 154)
      - Miscellanea (Box 154)
      - Program (Box 154)
      - Registration (Box 154)
    - 1983 Washington, DC
      - Planning (Box 154)
      - Program (Box 155)
    - 1984 Philadelphia, PA
      - Correspondence (Box 155)
      - Evaluations (Box 155)
      - Final Report (Box 155)
      - Invitation (Box 155)
        (includes ms. notes)
      - Planning
        - Timeline, Change Point Schedule, and Conference Manual (Box 155)
      - Preliminary Program (Box 155)
        (includes 1983 Preliminary Program and correspondence)
      - Publicity (Box 155)
      - Registration Lists (Box 155)
      - General, 3 folders (Box 155)
    - 1984 Mid-Year Meeting: Bloomington, IN (Box 155)
    - 1985 Las Vegas, NV (Box 155)
    - 1985 Mid-Year Meeting: Ft. Lauderdale, FL (Box 155)
    - 1986 Chicago, IL (Box 155)
    - 1987 Boston, MA
      - Conference Notebook (Box 155)
      - Correspondence (Box 155)
      - Reports (Box 155)
    - 1988 Mid-Year Meeting: Ann Arbor, MI
      - Call for papers, 1987 (Box 155)
      - General (Box 155)
    - 1989
      - Annual Business Meeting
        - Notes, October 1989 (Box 155)
          (possibly Peter Solomon's or Dick Hill's)
    - 1989 Mid-Year Meeting: San Diego, CA
      - Abstracts (Box 155)
        (contains meeting program)
    - 1990 Mid-Year Meeting: Ft. Lauderdale, FL
      - Abstracts (Box 155)
      - Handout (Box 155)
      - Reports, 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 155)
    - 1991 Mid-Year Meeting: Santa Clara, CA
      - Final Program (Box 155)
    - 1992 Mid-Year Meeting: Albuquerque, NM.
      - Financial Information (Box 155)
      - Proceedings (Box 155)
    - 1993 Columbus, OH (Box 156)
    - 1993 Mid-Year Meeting: Knoxville, TN: Financial Information (Box 156)
    - : Alexandria, VA (Box 156)
    - 1994 Mid-Year Meeting: Portland, OR (Box 156)
    - 1995 Chicago, IL (Box 156)
    - 1995 Mid-Year Meeting: Minneapolis, MN (Box 156)
    - 1996 Baltimore, MD (Box 156)
    - 1996 Mid-Year Meeting: San Diego, CA (Box 156)
    - 2000 Information Architecture Summit: Boston, MA: Materials for Reading/Handouts (Box 156)
    - 2001 Information Architecture Summit: San Francisco, CA: Handouts and Supplementary Materials (Box 156)
- RELATED ORGANIZATIONS AND SUBJECTS
  The RELATED ORGANIZATIONS AND SUBJECTS series (14 linear feet) is made up of materials about other organizations that are interested in information, information storage, and its transferal. Examples of such organizations include the American Federation of Information Processing Societies, American Library Association, American National Standards Committee, Catholic University Home Study Program, Information Industry Association, International Federation for Documentation, National Commission on Libraries and Information Science, and Special Libraries Association. Most of these organizations had liaison relationships with ASIS. Material regarding the White House Conference on Library and Information Services is included.
  Also included in this series are subject files, pertaining to some aspect of information science, amassed by ASIS officers or staff but without a clear link to any one committee, unit, or outside organization.
  - ADI Newsletter Symposium, 1965 (Box 157)
  - Africa Centre for Information Services, 1985 (Box 157)
  - Academic Press, 1972 (Box 157)
  - Access Information, Inc., 1980 (Box 157)
  - Affirmative Action Register, 1979 (Box 157)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS)
    - Annual Meeting
      - San Francisco, 1974 (Box 157)
      - New York, 1975 (Box 157)
      - Boston, 1976 (Box 157)
      - Denver, 1977 (Box 157)
      - Washington, D.C, 1978 (Box 157)
      - Houston, 1979 (Box 157)
      - San Francisco, 1980 (Box 157)
    - Consortium of Affiliates, 1980 (Box 157)
    - General Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 157)
      (years 1974-1977 include handbook; year 1979 includes summary report)
  - American Chemical Society (ACS), 1976-1977 (Box 157)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1940 1947 (Box 157)
  - American Federation of Information Processing Societies (AFIPS)
    - ASIS Membership Audits, 1982-1985 (Box 157)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1988 and undated, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1982, 12 folders (Box 157)
    - Directors Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 157)
    - Directory, 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Directory of Speakers on History of Computing, 1982 (Box 157)
    - Education Committee, 1970-1981 (Box 157)
    - Education Projects, 1983-1988 (Box 157)
    - Executive Directors Round Table, 1975 (Box 157)
    - Financial Information, 1965-1972 1984-1985 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box 157)
    - Government Activities, 1988 (Box 157)
    - Headquarters Newsletters, 1973-1981, 5 folders (Box 157)
    - Master Calendar of Information Processing Meetings, 1975-1981 (Box 158)
    - News Releases, 1976-1982 (Box 158)
    - Reports, 1985-1987, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Reports to ASIS Board, 1983-1988 (Box 158)
    - Status Reports, 1983-1988, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - Technology in Education, 1985-1986 (Box 158)
    - Washington Activities Committee, 1977 (Box 158)
    - Washington Reports, 1976-1982, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - White House Briefings, 1978-1979 (Box 158)
    - General, 1984-1985 1989, 2 folders (Box 158)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1970-1971 (Box 158)
  - American Institute of Physics, 1965-1966 and 1977 (Box 158)
  - American Library Association (ALA)
    - Accreditation Project, 1984-1988, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - Annual Conference, Detroit, 1970 (Box 158)
    - Book Fellows Project, 1986-1988 (Box 158)
    - Committee on the Status of Women in Librarianship, 1981 (Box 158)
    - Correspondence
      - Regarding ASIS Participation at ALA Convention, 1971-1973 (Box 158)
      - Regarding Opportunities for Advanced Study and CASES (Center for Advanced Study in Information Science), 1972-1978 (Box 158)
    - ERIC Clearinghouse on Library and Information Science, 1968-1972 (Box 158)
    - Financial Assistance for Library Education, 1983-1984 (Box 158)
    - General Correspondence, 1970 and 1972-1980, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Information Science and Automation Division (ISAD)
      - Symposium, 1969-1971 (Box 158)
    - Library Administration and Management Association (LAMA), 1985 (Box 158)
    - Library Information Technology Association (LITA), 1985
      - Telecommunications Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 158)
    - New York World's Fair Library Exhibit with SLA and ASIS, 1964 (Box 158)
    - General, 1984-1988 (Box 158)
  - American Medical Writers Association, undated (Box 159)
  - American National Standards Committee
    (see also Standards Committee in Committees series)
    - Z-39
      - Bylaws, Amendments and Additions, 1979-1980 (Box 159)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976
        - Committees Financial, 1979-1980 (Box 159)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 159)
        - Nominating, 1979-1980 (Box 159)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 159)
      - Draft Standards, 1976-1978 (Box 159)
      - Newsletter
        - News about Z-39 (Box 159)
        - Voice of Z-39, 1979-1980 (Box 159)
      - Secretariat Transfer to ASIS, 1975 (Box 159)
      - Subcommittee I Program, 1975 (Box 159)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association, 1977 (Box 159)
  - American Revolutionary Bicentennial Administration, 1975 (Box 159)
  - American Society for Cybernetics Forum, 1974-1981, 2 folders (Box 159)
  - American Society of Association Executives (ASAE), 1972-1978 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box 159)
  - American Society of Indexers, undated (Box 159)
    (includes "Directory of Courses on Indexing in Canada and the United States")
  - American University, 1978 (Box 159)
  - American University School of Government and Public Administration, 1959 (Box 159)
  - Applied Communication Research, 1975 (Box 159)
  - Architecture and Engineering Performance Information Center, 1983 (Box 159)
  - Archival Informatics Newsletter, 1988 (Box 159)
  - Asia Foundation, 1985 (Box 159)
  - Aspen Systems Corporation, 1974 (Box 159)
  - Associated Information Managers (AIM), 1987 (Box 159)
  - ASLIB (Association of Special Libraries and Information Bureaux)
    - Annual Report, 1976 (Box 159)
    - Brochures, 1977-1978 (Box 159)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 159)
  - Association for Computing Machinery (ACM), 1967-1974 1978 1989 (Box 159)
  - Association for Information and Image Management (AIIM), 1989 (Box 159)
  - Association for Systems Management (ASM), 1978-1980 (Box 159)
  - Association of Colleges and Research Libraries (ACRL), 1985 (Box 159)
  - Association for the Development of Religious Information System (ADRIS), 1973-1976 (Box 159)
    (includes directory and newsletters)
  - Association of Data Processing Service Organizations, 1977-1980 (Box 159)
  - Association of Interface Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 159)
  - Association of Independent Information Professionals, (AIIP), 1988-1992, 2 folders (Box 159)
  - Association of Record Managers and Administrators, Inc. (ARMA), 1984-1986 1988-1989 (Box 159)
  - Association of Research Libraries, 1973 (Box 159)
  - Association of Scientific Information Dissemination Centers (ASIDIC), 1973 (Box 159)
  - Association Friends, 1979 (Box 159)
  - Auerbach, 1975 (Box 159)
  - Baltimore Region Institutional Studies Center (BRISC), 1975 (Box 159)
  - Battelle, 1974-1976 (Box 159)
  - Bio-Sciences Information Service, 1975-1976 (Box 159)
  - Bowker, R.R.: regarding Bowker Annual, 1975-1980 (Box 159)
  - Canadian Association for Information Science
    - General Information, 1970-1982 (Box 159)
    - Membership Lists, 1973 (Box 159)
    - Newsletters, 1971-1974 (Box 159)
  - Catholic University Home Study Program
    - Agreement, 1976 (Box 160)
    - Bibliographic Support, November 1971-December 1975, 5 folders (Box 160)
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 160)
    - Correspondence
      - Regarding Establishment and Administration, 1974-1977 (Box 160)
      - Regarding Reprint Rights, 1976-1977 (Box 160)
      - Requesting Information about Program, 1976-1977 (Box 160)
    - Marketing, 1976 (Box 160)
    - Minutes, 1975 (Box 160)
    - Modules
      - I, Motivation in the Organizational Setting, undated (Box 160)
      - I, Papers on Motivation, 1975-1976 (Box 160)
      - II, 1976 (Box 160)
        (includes readings)
      - II-IV, 1976 (Box 160)
    - Registrants, 1976 (Box 160)
    - Reports: on the Motivation Module, 1976 (Box 160)
  - Center for Office Technology, 1985 (Box 160)
  - Center for Program Development and the Handicapped, 1975-1976 (Box 160)
  - Center for Strategic International Studies (CSIS) (Box 160)
  - Central Documentation Program, Central Air Documents Office (CADO): joint Navy-Air Force program, ca. 1948 (Box 160)
    (Eugene B. Jackson's copy of a manual)
  - Chemical Abstracts Service, 1982 (Box 160)
  - China, 1980 (Box 160)
  - Civil Service, 1969 and 1972 regarding Classification and Salary Schedule (Box 160)
  - Coalition on Government Information, 1988 (Box 160)
  - Commission on New Technological Uses of Copyrighted Works, National (CONTU), ca. 1974 and 1978 (Box 160)
  - Commission on Software Issues, 1980-1984 (Box 160)
  - Committee on Scientific and Technical Information, 1965-1972 (Box 160)
  - Committee to Investigate Copyright Problems Affecting the Communication of Scientific and Educational Information, Inc. (CICP)
    (primarily Gerald Sophar's files)
    - Copyright, 1958-1959 (Box 160)
    - Corporate Documents, 1960-1973 (Box 160)
    - Tax Documents
      [Restricted until 2048; removed to box 188]
      - Taxes Paid, 1966 (Box 160)
      - Tax Returns, 1969-1970 (Box 160)
      - Tax-Exempt Application, 1967-1973 (Box 160)
  - Computer in American Education, Conference on, 1965-1966 (Box 160)
  - Computer Readable Bibliographic Data Bases
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1976-1980, 2 folders (Box 160)
  - The Computer Workshop of Northern Virginia, Inc., 1980 (Box 160)
  - Conference on Foreign Journals, ADI, 1942 (Box 160)
  - Conference on Population and Housing Census Users, 1965-1968 (Box 160)
  - Conference on the History and Heritage of Science and Information Systems, 1999 (Box 160)
  - Congressional Clearinghouse on the Future, 1977-1980 (Box 160)
  - Continuing Library Education Network and Exchange (CLENE)
    - Abstract, 1976 (Box 161)
    - Continuing Education Communicator, 1980 (Box 161)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box 161)
    - Minutes, 1976 (Box 161)
    - Newsletters, 1975-1976 and 1980 (Box 161)
    - Reports
      - Final, 1975-1976 (Box 161)
      - Monthly and Quarterly, 1975-1976 (Box 161)
  - Contracts, 1980 (Box 161)
  - Conversion of Serials Project (CONSER), 1973-1976 (Box 161)
  - Copyright, 1976 1979-1981 1986-1989, 3 folders (Box 161)
  - Copyright Clearance Center, Inc. (CCCI)
    - First Year Operating Experience, 1979 (Box 161)
    - Handbook for Serial Publishers, 1977-1978 (Box 161)
    - News Releases and Brochures, 1979 (Box 161)
  - Copyright Revision Bill, 1976-1977 (Box 161)
  - Corporate Ownership and Position Statement (COPS), 1977 (Box 161)
  - Corporate Ownership Reports Access (CORA), 1976-1977 (Box 161)
  - Corporation for Open Systems, (COS), 1988 (Box 161)
  - Council for Computerized Library Networks (CCLN), 1979 (Box 161)
  - The Council for Exceptional Children, 1974 (Box 161)